<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Motonari Kambara</title>
    <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Motonari Kambara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description> M. Kambara and K. Sugiura, “Case Relation Transformer: A Crossmodal Language Generation Model for Fetching Instructions”, IEEE Robotics and Automation Letters, Vol. 6, Issue 4, pp. 8371-8378, 2021. DOI: 10.1109/LRA.2021.3107026 PDF  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>International Conference</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/inter_conf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/inter_conf/</guid>
      <description>R. Korekata, M. Kambara, Y. Yoshida, S. Ishikawa, Y. Kawasaki, M. Takahashi and K. Sugiura, “Switching Head–Tail Funnel UNITER for Dual Referring Expression Comprehension with Fetch-and-Carry Tasks”, IEEE/RSJ IROS, 2023. PDF K. Kaneda, R. Korekata, Y. Wada, S. Nagashima, M. Kambara, Y. Iioka, H. Matsuo, Y. Imai, T. Nishimura, and K. Sugiura, “DialMAT: Dialogue-Enabled Transformer with Moment-Based Adversarial Training”, CVPR 2023 Embodied AI Workshop, 2023. PDF M. Kambara and K.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Award</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/award/</guid>
      <description> K. Kaneda, R. Korekata, Y. Wada, S. Nagashima, M. Kambara, Y. Iioka, H. Matsuo, Y. Imai, T. Nishimura, K. Sugiura, CVPR 2023 Embodied AI Workshop DialFRED Challenge 1st Prize, 6/19/2023. M. Kambara, Y. Yoshida, K. Kaneda, S. Otsuki, R. Korekata, H. Matsuo, Y. Wada, W. Yang, K. Sugiura, Honorable Mention Award, REVERIE Challenge @ CSIG 2022, 8/19/2022.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domestic Conference</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/domestic_conf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/domestic_conf/</guid>
      <description>平野慎之助, 小松拓実, 和田唯我, 神原元就, 畑中駿平, 平川翼, 山下隆義, 藤吉弘亘, 杉浦孔明: “ENCHANT: 大規模言語モデルを用いた仮説生成に基づくクロスモーダル説明文生成”, 第41回日本ロボット学会学術講演会, 1K4-03, 2023. 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “マルチモーダル言語処理に基づくfetch-and-carryタスクの自動化と実行”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 2I6-OS-4a-03, 2023. 兼田寛大, 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “Learning to Rank Physical Objects: ランキング学習による物理世界検索エンジン”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 3G1-OS-24a-01, 2023. 小松拓実, 神原元就, 畑中駿平, 松尾榛夏, 平川翼, 山下隆義, 藤吉弘亘, 杉浦孔明: “Nearest Neighbor Future Captioning:物体配置タスクにおける衝突リスクに関する説明文生成”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 3G1-OS-24a-05, 2023. 是方諒介, 神原元就, 吉田悠, 石川慎太朗, 川崎陽祐, 髙橋正樹, 杉浦孔明: “Switching Head–Tail Funnel UNITERによる対象物体および配置目標に関する指示文理解と物体操作”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 2G4-OS-21d-01, 2023. 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “記号接地されたfetch-and-carryタスクの自動化と実行”, 第40回日本ロボット学会学術講演会, 4I1-01, 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
