<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Motonari Kambara</title>
    <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Motonari Kambara</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <atom:link href="https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/journal/</guid>
      <description>T. Komatsu, M. Kambara, S. Hatanaka, H. Matsuo, T. Hirakawa, T. Yamashita, H. Fujiyoshi, and K. Sugiura, “Nearest Neighbor Future Captioning: Generating Descriptions for Possible Collisions in Object Placement Tasks”, Advanced Robotics, 2024, to appear. K. Kaneda, S. Nagashima, R. Korekata, M. Kambara, and K. Sugiura, “Learning-To-Rank Approach for Identifying Everyday Objects Using a Physical-World Search Engine”, IEEE Robotics and Automation Letters, Vol. 9, Issue 3, pp. 2088-2095, 2024. DOI: 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Conference</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/inter_conf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/inter_conf/</guid>
      <description>K. Kaneda, S. Nagashima, R. Korekata, M. Kambara, and K. Sugiura, “Learning-To-Rank Approach for Identifying Everyday Objects Using a Physical-World Search Engine”, IEEE RAL presented at IEEE/RSJ IROS, 2024, to appear. DOI: 10.1109/LRA.2024.3352363 T. Nishimura, K. Kuyo, M. Kambara, and K. Sugiura, “Object Segmentation from Open-Vocabulary Manipulation Instructions Based on Optimal Transport Polygon Matching with Multimodal Foundation Models”, IEEE/RSJ IROS, 2024, to appear. M. Kambara, C. Hori, K. Sugiura, K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/award/</guid>
      <description> K. Kaneda, R. Korekata, Y. Wada, S. Nagashima, M. Kambara, Y. Iioka, H. Matsuo, Y. Imai, T. Nishimura, K. Sugiura, CVPR 2023 Embodied AI Workshop DialFRED Challenge 1st Prize, 6/19/2023. M. Kambara, Y. Yoshida, K. Kaneda, S. Otsuki, R. Korekata, H. Matsuo, Y. Wada, W. Yang, K. Sugiura, Honorable Mention Award, REVERIE Challenge @ CSIG 2022, 8/19/2022. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domestic Conference</title>
      <link>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/domestic_conf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://motonarikambara.github.io/publications/domestic_conf/</guid>
      <description>松尾榛夏, 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “マルチモーダル基盤モデルと劣モジュラ最適化に基づく移動ロボットの環境探索”, 2024年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 4O3-OS-16e-03, 2024. 齋藤大地, 神原元就, 九曜克之, 杉浦孔明: “マルチモーダルLLMおよび視覚言語基盤モデルに基づく大規模物体操作データセットにおけるタスク成功判定”, 2024年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 3O1-OS-16b-02, 2024. 西村喬行, 九曜克之, 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “マルチモーダル基盤モデルと最適輸送を用いたポリゴンマッチングによる参照表現セグメンテーション”, 2024年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 2O6-OS-16a-02, 2024. 平野慎之助, 小松拓実, 和田唯我, 神原元就, 畑中駿平, 平川翼, 山下隆義, 藤吉弘亘, 杉浦孔明: “ENCHANT: 大規模言語モデルを用いた仮説生成に基づくクロスモーダル説明文生成”, 第41回日本ロボット学会学術講演会, 1K4-03, 2023. 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “マルチモーダル言語処理に基づくfetch-and-carryタスクの自動化と実行”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 2I6-OS-4a-03, 2023. 兼田寛大, 神原元就, 杉浦孔明: “Learning to Rank Physical Objects: ランキング学習による物理世界検索エンジン”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 3G1-OS-24a-01, 2023. 小松拓実, 神原元就, 畑中駿平, 松尾榛夏, 平川翼, 山下隆義, 藤吉弘亘, 杉浦孔明: “Nearest Neighbor Future Captioning:物体配置タスクにおける衝突リスクに関する説明文生成”, 2023年度 人工知能学会全国大会, 3G1-OS-24a-05, 2023.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
